<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-08-30T12:22:02-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Karina Makhani</title><subtitle>Personal site</subtitle><author><name>Karina Makhani</name></author><entry><title type="html">Why I’m writing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/08/30/why-im-writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I’m writing" /><published>2025-08-30T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-08-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/08/30/why-im-writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/08/30/why-im-writing.html"><![CDATA[<p>I graduate in May of 2026. Only 8 months until I’m officially in the real world! I’ve spent a lot of time over the past few months thinking of what comes next, especially career-wise, which has led me to reflect on important people in my career. For whatever reason,
a lot of mentors and people I admire career-wise seem to engage in the habit of documenting their work on some kind of blog. And that’s why I’m writing here!</p>

<p>I think a lot of people I went to high school with would be kind of shocked I majored in Computer Science and not English, or something English-related. If there was one thing I was known for, I would say it was my writing. In High School, I was a part of a 3-year writing-intensive program, and I was the Editor-in-Chief of our print newspaper. In college, for one reason or another, I didn’t continue with writing in any form. I thought it wasn’t useful for pursuing software engineering, which is ironic considering I’ve spent weeks writing documents in all three of my internships. And now I’m committing to writing on a blog, so maybe this is full circle.</p>

<p>So, for the sake of following in the footsteps of those I admire, documenting my work and my learnings, and reigniting an old passion, I created this blog and will hopefully use it. Thanks for taking a look!</p>]]></content><author><name>Karina Makhani</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I graduate in May of 2026. Only 8 months until I’m officially in the real world! I’ve spent a lot of time over the past few months thinking of what comes next, especially career-wise, which has led me to reflect on important people in my career. For whatever reason, a lot of mentors and people I admire career-wise seem to engage in the habit of documenting their work on some kind of blog. And that’s why I’m writing here!]]></summary></entry></feed>